The idea is that many of you are now
upgrading
and in the idea of fourth density
reality will reach a general average of
the low 200,000s.
And as you thus then as we are doing go
up the ladder so to speak and become
more the idea of quasi physical beings,
you'll come closer and closer and closer
on average to the idea of the 333,000
cycle per second frequency domain. But
the idea is that pi is a factor of that.
Right? Thus then if you begin there with
pi as a seedling and begin to amplify
it, you will amplify it in such a manner
with that as the original basis that you
will thus then be a harmonic
of the higher frequency. And it will in
a sense be easier to transition and
shift from parallel world to parallel
world that contains the harmonic of that
frequency to allow you to feel the
acceleration in a more visceral way.
>> Kind of like catching a wave, huh?
>> Yes. Exactly.
>> When you talked about the space-time
resonator,
>> Yes.
>> you mentioned that that frequency was
the was the frequency used for achieving
the tunneling effect.
And I'm wondering about that because the
space-time resonator also appears to be
a way to to bring energy down from
spaceime. Yeah,
>> we said it is a step down transformer.
>> The energy that flows through the
space-time resonator is is not an
electron type energy, isn't it?
>> No. Although it can be converted into
such.
>> In the conversion, is it would it be
would it work to use an inductive
method? In other words, to create the
speime resonator, which is a closed
loop.
>> Yes.
>> And then wrap around that another kind
of coil, a reactant coil,
>> because that's how you have to siphon
the energy off and translate it into a
form of energy that you can use.
>> That's what I thought.
>> Yes.
>> In in building that apparatus is what
would change the nature of the energy by
the
windings per meter. In other words, if I
had a coil that said had say five
windings per meter.
>> Yes.
>> What would that do in and differently
than one that say had 30 windings per
meter? Like a higher rate of winding.
What would be
>> it would be something that you could
finetune
more easily rather than simply having a
coarse translation.
>> Right? So the the lower winding is a
coarser form of
>> and thus in a sense
>> less usable or less controllable.
>> Okay. So it would make sense.
>> It would act as a form of high volume
release capacitor
discharging all at once. It could cause
a little damage.
>> I see. But the more windings, the finer
the tuning, the more you have the
ability to tune the frequency to exactly
the pitch you wish.
>> Kind of like a higher resolution of
control. And in controlling it, do we
change the physical length of the wire
to tune it or can I just use a reactant
circuit to do that? like a capacitor
resistor circuit.
>> You can use that if you wish, but you
will have to find a new design other
than the ones that exist on your planet
at this time. And we have already
actually described this as a series of
nested capacitors of certain volume and
certain shape that create certain
resonant frequencies within one the
other.
>> That's in one of the other
transmissions.
>> Yes, it is.
>> Nested capacitors. That's really
interesting.
>> Yes, it is.
>> Because the space-time resonator is a
nested coil.
>> Yes, it is. It's starting to make sense.
>> Thank you. It's about time. [laughter]
>> We're kind of thick at this point in our
track.
>> No, that's all right. I wasn't making a
reference to that. I was giving you more
information. It's about time.
>> Oh, it's about time and frequency.
>> Yes.
>> Interesting.